[{"answer": "How you feelin', my friend", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Feeling hot", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Up I would say... What would you say", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Up ribbon", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Down I would say... What would you say", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Down ribbon", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I just wait. For this... It's what I wait for... I wait all year", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " You do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Fucking A", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " You have to think about the shot. It's the shot. The shot's it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Yeah... I guess", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know... I guess I think about the deer... Being out, maybe. I don't know. I think about it all. Hell, I like the trees, you know? I like the ways the trees are, all the different ways the trees are too", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You gotta hit it here. Here, my friend, not there", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Here. Hit it here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " What'd he say", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Pow", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Pow", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Pow", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Uh... well, maybe you could tell us how it is over there", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Pow", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Pow", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Pow", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You got it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "She fucked you", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "She fucked me too", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Here! This is it", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It is too! Now you passed it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "This is it. Definitely. This is it, but they changed it", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Who's full of shit", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You're full of shit", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're full of shit", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm telling you, they changed it", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "They did too", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Then lemme have 'em", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " No!!!", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'll get the boots", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " I mean let's get going before", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "my friend!  my friend... Goddamn it, my friend, don't you know anything", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Sure. Sure, my friend. We're going home", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Ah yes. Of course... So few survive.  La creme de la creme... How did you obtain release", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Playing", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "But you must come in", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "But I insist", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's gotta be the next one. I mean it's gotta be! Right, my friend", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "It's gotta", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "But", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I made you a sweater.  Here... You have to take that off", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What the", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "my friend...?  Jesus, my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Worse since she talked to who", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Talked to my friend?  my friend's alive", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend, you ever do it with one of those slants", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "No", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Who's going", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " my friend,we're going huntin'", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "We're all going", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Who's going", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "my friend's going", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I know! I fuckin' know", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "I do!!", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "You don't", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I'm tellin' you she does it, my friend! With twenty guys you know", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I do!!", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "She does not", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Then what's the gun for! What's this for", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "In case???!!! In case of what? In case you stumble on her, suckin' cock in the front fucking hall?", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "In case???!!! In case of what? In case you stumble on her, suckin' cock in the front fucking hall?", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "She does, my friend! That's what I'm telling you! She does!!", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "You loaded it, my friend! I saw you", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "The fuck you didn't!... Gimme that", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Here", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "my friend, yes", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " Lieutenant my friend! Lieutenant my friend report to the ramp", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Right this way, Lieutenant", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Where is he??", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " You are his friend", "docId": "Deer-Hunter_-The.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": " my friend is under his tree... Beside the terrace. You can't miss him", "qsentId": 82}]